

VICTOR BRIAND

WEB DEVELOPER FULL STACK

HTML • CSS • JS • PHP MYSQL • JQUERY • BOOTSTRAP WORDPRESS • JMERISE

CONTACT

https://victorbriand.github.io/ victor.briand78@gmail.com + 33 6 69 98 36 98 21, rue Louis Chagnot 78350 Jouy-en-josas

LANGUAGE

French Mother tongue
Portuguese Mother tongue
English Fluent
Spanish Fluent
German Studying

SKILLS

Pack Office Pack Adobe (Ps, Ai, Pr, Ae, Lr) Unity 2D

HOBBIES

Video game creation informatic Video and Photo Editing Photography Traveling Sports

PROFIL

Currently training in web development, I am looking for an internship that will allow me to increase my knowledge in this field. My 10 years of experience in a company have allowed me to acquire valuable capacities, such as management and teamwork, rigour, and communication. I would now like to put these skills and the abilities I acquired during my training to good use in your company.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

CEFII - Higher Web SchoolSince Novembre 2020 | Angers (49) France

Web Developement and Web Mobile Full Stack
 (BTEC Higher National Diploma equivalent)
 HTML • CSS • JS • PHP • JQuery • Bootstrap •
 Wordpress • Merise • UML • AJAX • GIT • ANGULAR • IONIQ

TECOMAH - Environment School Jouy-en-josas (78) France

- June 2013 | Youth Pastry Training
- **June 2012** | BTEC Gastronomy, Organisation and Production
- **June 2011** | BTEC First Diploma, Gastronomy, Organisation and Production

WORK HISTORY

2015 - 2020 | SECOND DE CUISINE TF1 - Club de Direction « Le Club TF1 » | FRANCE

- Creativity et innovation
- Team Management
- Apprenticeship manager
- Event management

2013 - 2014 | Pastry Chef

2012 - 2013 | Apprentice Pastry

2009 - 2012 | Apprentice Cook